A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Executive Vice-President, William E. Lavery, 1968-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- V.P. of Finance Materials, 1968-1971
  - Student Affairs - Student Center, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
  - Student Affairs - Student Fees, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Student Affairs - Student Forums Board, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Student Affairs - Student Government Association, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Student Affairs - Student Life Policies, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 16-17)
  - Student Affairs - Student Loans, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Student Affairs - Student Union, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Student Affairs - Civilian Marching Board, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Student Affairs - Student Publications, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Student Affairs - Fraternity-Sorority System, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Student Affairs - Crisis Center, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Tech Festival - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Town of Blacksburg - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Treasurer's Office - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 26-27)
  - University Development - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - VPI Centennial - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - VPI Facilities, INC. - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - VPI Programs - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - YMCA - General, 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - V.P. of Finance Materials Restricted Documents, 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted
- Correspondence, 1969-1973
  - Biennial Budget - General, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Community College System, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Lease Agreements, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - SCHEV - Finance Advisory Comm., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - Scholarships, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 366)
  - Special Programs, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - TIAA - CREF, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Policy, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Biennial Budget, 1972-1974, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - Budget Instructions, 1972-1974, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - General Counsel, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 373)
  - Board of Visitors, Financial Reports, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 374)
  - Community College System, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - Computer Orientation Administrative Staff, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - EDUCOM, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Lease Agreements, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - SCHEV - Finance Advisory Comm., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Computing Center Applications, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - Student Budget Board Contingency Account, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - Personnel - General, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - Policy, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - Student Enrollment Projections, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - Student Loans, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Financial Reports, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - Biennial Budget, 1972-1974 - Division of Budget, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - Biennial Budget, 1972-1974, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - Biennial Budget 1972-1974 - Charts, Tables, etc., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 391)
  - Appropriations Hearings, 1972-1974, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - Budget and Allotments - General, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Budget Instructions, 1972-1974, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 394)
  - President T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 395)
  - Graduate School, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 396)
  - Business Manager, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 397)
  - Alumni Association - General, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 398)
  - General Counsel, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 399)
  - Capital Outlay (Projects and Budgets), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 400)
  - Capital Outlay Requests, 1972-1974, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 401)
  - Capital Outlay Requests, 1974-1976, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - Equipment Aquisition Approval, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 403)
  - Institutional Research Office, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 404)
  - Student Enrollment Projections, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 405)
  - Proposals - Computing Center, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 406)
  - SCHEV - Finance Advisory Comm., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Planning Management Systems Training Seminar - Williamsburg, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - SCHEV - Student Financial Aid Comm., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 409)
  - Residence Hall Federation, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 410)
  - Student Budget Board Contingency Account, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 411)
  - Student Budget Board - General, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 412)
  - Special Programs, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 413)
  - Blacksburg Community Federation, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 414)
  - General, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 415)
  - EACUBO, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 416)
  - National Institute for Academic Deans and Business Officers, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 417)
  - Personnel - General, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 418)
  - Physical Plant Planning, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 419)
  - Policy, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 420)
  - Travel, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 421)
  - SREB Contracts, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 422)
  - Student Budget Board - Finance, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 423)
  - Student Life Policies, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 424)
  - Student Organizations, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 425)
  - State Technical Services, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 426)
  - Task Force on Extension, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 427)
  - Information Division, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 428)
  - Research Division, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 429)
  - Accounting - General, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 430)
  - Financial Reports, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 431)
  - Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 432)
  - Appropriations, Budgetary Items, etc., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 433)
  - Division of Budget - Richmond, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 434)
  - Accounting Hearings, 1972-1974, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 435)
  - Biennial Budget, 1972-1974, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 436)
  - Biennial Budget, 1972-1974 - Appropriations #1, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 437)
  - Biennial Budget, 1972-1974 - Appropriations #2, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 438)
  - Motion Picture Authorization, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 439)
  - Budget Instructions, 1972-1974, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 440)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 441)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 442)
  - Administrative Staff Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 443)
  - Administrative General (Civil Rights, Etc.), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 444)
  - Governor's Management Study, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 445)
  - Administration - Space Needs, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 446)
  - Governor's Office, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 447)
  - Secretary of Education, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 448)
  - President T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 449)
  - College of Home Economics, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 450)
  - Summer School, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 451)
  - Graduate School, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 452)
  - Learning Resources Center, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 453)
  - President's Visits to Depts., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 454)
  - Executive Vice President, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 455)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 456)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 457)
  - Vice President for Finance, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 458)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 459)
  - Exec. Assistant to President, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 460)
  - Business Manager, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 461)
  - Administrative Intern, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 462)
  - Alumni Association, General, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 463)
  - Athletic Association, General, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 464)
  - Book Store, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 465)
  - Dormitories, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 466)
  - Electric Service Department, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 467)
  - Auxiliary Eneterprises, General, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 468)
  - Motor Pool, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 469)
  - Centralized Mailing, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 470)
  - Board of Visitors, Financial Reports, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 471)
  - Board of Visitors Correspondence, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 472)
  - Board of Visitors Reports, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 473)
  - Buildings and Grounds, General, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 474)
  - TV Cable System, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 475)
  - Capital Outlay (Projects and Budgets), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 476)
  - College of Agriculturem, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 477)
  - College of Architecture, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 478)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 479)
  - College of Business, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 480)
  - College of Education, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 481)
  - State Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 482)
  - College of Engineering, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 483)
  - Building Committee, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 484)
  - Computer Committee, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 485)
  - University Committees - General, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 486)
  - Patent Committee, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 487)
  - Community College System, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 488)
  - Administrative Systems Computing Center, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 489)
  - Computer Allotment, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 490)
  - Computer Orientation Administrative Staff, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 491)
  - Computing Center, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 492)
  - Data Processing, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 493)
  - EDUCOM, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 494)
  - Equipment Acquistion Approval, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 495)
  - Management Information System, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 496)
  - Regional Computing Center, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 497)
  - FARMSNET, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 498)
  - Automated Library System, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 499)
  - Systems Development Computing Center, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 500)
  - Computer Assisted Instruction, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 501)
  - Extension Division, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 502)
  - Continuing Education Center, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 503)
  - Reston Project, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 504)
  - Venezuela Project, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 505)
  - SCHEV, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 506)
  - Finance Advisory Comm., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 507)
  - General Professionial Advisory Council, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 508)
  - Northern Virginia Consortium, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 509)
  - General Assembly Commission on Higher Education, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 510)
  - Higher Education Act of 1972, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 511)
  - SCHEV - Student Financial Aid Comm., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 512)
  - Admissions and Registrar, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 513)
  - Commencement, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 514)
  - Student Affairs General, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 515)
  - Infirmary, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 516)
  - Residence Hall Federation, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 517)
  - ROTC, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 518)
  - Student Budget Board Contingency Account, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 519)
  - Scholarships, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 520)
  - Student Budget Board Financial Records, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 521)
  - Student Budget Board - General, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 522)
  - Purchasing, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 523)
  - Dean's Meeting, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 524)
  - Administrator's Conference, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 525)
  - Land-Grant College Meeting, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 526)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 527)
  - Special Programs, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 528)
  - Blacksburg Community Federation, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 529)
  - General, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 530)
  - National Association of College and University Administrators, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 531)
  - EACUBO, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 532)
  - AAUP, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 533)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 534)
  - National Institute for College and University Administrators, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 535)
  - National Institute for Academic Deans and Business Officers, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 536)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 537)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 538)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 539)
  - Dismissals/Personnel, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 540)
  - State Division of Personnel, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 541)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 542)
  - Personnel - General, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 543)
  - Job Applications, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 544)
  - Faculty Tenure and Promotions, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 545)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 546)
  - Automated Payroll System, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 547)
  - Insurance, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 548)
  - Unemployment, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 549)
  - Physical Plant Planning, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 550)
  - Policy, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 551)
  - Travel, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 552)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 553)
  - Geology Grant, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 554)
  - Grants and Proposals - General, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 555)
  - National Science Foundation, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 556)
  - Vet School, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 557)
  - SREB Contracts, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 558)
  - Law Enforcement Education Program, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 559)
  - Library, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 560)
  - Proposals, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 561)
  - Research Council Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 562)
  - VPI Industry Center, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 563)
  - Glee Club, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 564)
  - Institutional Research Office, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 565)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 566)
  - Student Budget Board Finance, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 567)
  - Student Life Policies, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 568)
  - Student Center - Budget, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 569)
  - Student Fees, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 570)
  - Student Government Association, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 571)
  - Student Organization, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 572)
  - Student Records System, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 573)
  - Student Union, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 574)
  - Civilian Marching Band, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 575)
  - Student Publications, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 576)
  - Fraternity - Sorority System, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 577)
  - Crisis Center, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 578)
  - Student Constitutional Affairs Board, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 579)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 580)
  - University Development, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 581)
  - Division of Budget - Richmond, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 582)
  - Governor's Budget Advisory Board, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 583)
  - Biennial Budget, 1972-1974, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 584)
  - Motion Picture Authorization, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 585)
  - Budget and Allotments - General, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 586)
  - Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 587)
  - Financial Reports, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 588)
  - Funding, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 589)
  - Automated Accounting System, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 590)
  - Accounting - General, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 591)
  - President T. Marshall Hahn, Jr., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 592)
  - Rural Development Act of 1972, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 593)
  - Secretary of Education, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 594)
  - Governor's Office, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 595)
  - Offices/Personnel, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 596)
  - Legislative Tour, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 597)
  - Administrative Staff Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 598)
  - Administration General (Civil Rights, etc.), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 599)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 600)
  - Veterinary Medicine, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 601)
  - Learning Resources Center, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 602)
  - Graduate School, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 603)
  - Summer School, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6043)
  - Board of Visitors Correspondence, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 605)
  - University Airport, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 606)
  - Motor Pool, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 607)
  - Auxiliary Expenses - General, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 608)
  - Dormitories, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 609)
  - Book Store, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 610)
  - Athletics Association - General, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 611)
  - Alumni Association - General, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 612)
  - Administrative Intern, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 613)
  - Business Manager, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 614)
  - Executive Assistant to the President, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 615)
  - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 616)
  - Vice President for Finance, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 617)
  - Health and Safety Office, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 618)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 619)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 620)
  - Executive Vice President, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 621)
  - President's Visits to Departments, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 622)
  - College of Engineering, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 623)
  - Federal City College Agreement, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 624)
  - College of Education, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 625)
  - College of Business, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 626)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 627)
  - College of Architecture, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 628)
  - College of Agriculture, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 629)
  - Capital Outlay, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 630)
  - Capital Outlay (Projects and Budgets), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 631)
  - Board of Visitors, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 632)
  - Building Committee, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 633)
  - Computer Committee, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 634)
  - University Committees - General, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 635)
  - Judical Review Committee Appeals and Reports, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 636)
  - Patent Committee, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 637)
  - Community College System, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 638)
  - Adminstrative Systems Computing Center, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 639)
  - Computer Allotments, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 640)
  - Division of ADP, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 641)
  - ADP/Higher Education, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 642)
  - Computing Center, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 643)
  - Systems Development Computing Center, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 644)
  - Data Processing, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 645)
  - Equipment Acquistion Approval, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 646)
  - FARMSNET, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 647)
  - Extension Division, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 648)
  - Continuing Education Center, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 649)
  - Reston Project, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 650)
  - State Technical Services, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 651)
  - Task Force on Extension, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 652)
  - Research Division, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 653)
  - SCHEV, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 654)
  - The Virginia Plan - SCHEV, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 655)
  - SCHEV - Finance Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 656)
  - General Professional Council, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 657)
  - Southwest Regional Consortium, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 658)
  - Tidewater Consortium, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 659)
  - Northern Virginia Consortium, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 660)
  - Western Regional Consortium, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 661)
  - General Assembly's Commisson on Higher Education, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 662)
  - SCHEV - Student Financial Aid Committee, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 663)
  - Admissions and Registrar, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 664)
  - Commencement, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 665)
  - Student Affairs - General, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 666)
  - Honor Court, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 667)
  - Infirmary, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 668)
  - ROTC, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 669)
  - Student Budget Board Contingency, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 670)
  - Scholarships, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 671)
  - Student Budget Board Financial Records, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 672)
  - Student Budget Board - General, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 673)
  - VPI Industry Center, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 674)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 675)
  - Administrator's Conference, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 676)
  - National Assoc. Of State Univ. and Land-Grant Colleges, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 677)
  - Architectural Concerns, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 678)
  - Special Programs, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 679)
  - Lynchburg Baptist College, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 680)
  - Blacksburg Community Federation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 681)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 682)
  - National Institute for Academic Dean and Business Officers, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 683)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 684)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 685)
  - University Press of Virginia, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 686)
  - Information Division, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 687)
  - Proposals, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 688)
  - Glee Club, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 689)
  - Institutional Research Office, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 690)
  - Faculty Tenure and Promotions, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 691)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 692)
  - Automated Payroll System, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 693)
  - EEO, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 694)
  - Physical Plant Planning, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 695)
  - Job Applications, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 696)
  - National Association of Colleges and University Business Officers, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 697)
  - General, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 698)
  - Student Enrollment Projections, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 699)
  - Dismissals/Personnel, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 700)
  - Employee Benefits, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 701)
  - Insurance, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 702)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 703)
  - Personnel/General, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 704)
  - Vet School, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 705)
  - SREB Contracts, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 706)
  - Emminent Scholars, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 707)
  - Policy, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 708)
  - Travel, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 709)
  - Library, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 710)
  - Purchasing, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 711)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 712)
  - National Science Foundation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 713)
  - University Policy for Student Life, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 714)
  - Student Center - Budget, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 715)
  - Student Fees, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 716.)
  - Student Government Association, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 717)
  - Student Loans, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 718)
  - Student Organizations, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 719)
  - Student Records System, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 720)
  - Student Union, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 721)
  - Civilian Marching Band, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 722)
  - Student Publications, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 723)
  - Fraternity - Sorority System, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 724)
  - Crisis Center, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 725)
  - Student Constitutional Affairs, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 726)
  - Town of Blacksburg, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 727)
  - Treasurer's Office, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 728)
  - University Development, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 729)
  - VPTC, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 730)
  - Consulting, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 731)
  - Consulting Approved #1, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 732)
  - Consulting Approved #2, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 733)
- Operating Allotments, 1967-1973
  - Allotments #1, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 734)
  - Allotments #2, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 735)
  - Allotments #1, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 736)
  - Allotments #2, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 737)
  - Allotments #3, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 738)
  - Allotments #1, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 739)
  - Allotments #2, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 740)
  - Allotments #3, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 741)
  - Allotments #4, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 742)
  - Allotments #1, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 743)
  - Allotments #2, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 744)
  - Allotments #3, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 745)
  - Allotments #4, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 746)
  - Allotments #1, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 747)
  - Allotments #2, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 748)
  - Allotments #3, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 749)
  - Allotments #4, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 750)
  - Allotments #5, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 751)
  - Allotments #1, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 752)
  - Allotments #2, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 753)
  - Allotments #3, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 754)
  - Allotments #4, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 755)
  - Allotments #5, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 756)
  - Allotments #1, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Allotments #2, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Allotments #3, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Allotments #4, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Allotments #5, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Allotments #6, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Allotments #7, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)